Welcome to Stock Tracker! 

To be able to use the application, make sure you have XQuartz also downloaded
and working.

Make sure to have a Opam, OCaml, Libev, and pkg-config installed--you may be able to enter
"brew install opam ocaml libev pkg-config" into terminal, if Homebrew is installed.

Make sure to run "opam init." Then, install the necessary modules by running
"opam install cohttp lwt js_of_ocaml graphics csv conf-libev cohttp-lwt ounit ansiterminal qcheck cohttp-lwt-unix"
in your terminal window.  

After downloading the files and navigating into the directory, run "make build"
and then "make run".